{
  "questions": [
    {
      "qid": "p1u7-h1",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "There are ___________ apples.",
      "correctAnswer": "eleven"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u7-h2",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "There are ___________ lemons.",
      "correctAnswer": "thirteen"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u7-h3",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "There are ___________ peaches.",
      "correctAnswer": "eighteen"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u7-h4",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "There are ___________ cherries.",
      "correctAnswer": "fifteen"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u7-h5",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "There are ___________ oranges.",
      "correctAnswer": "nineteen"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u7-h6",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "There are ___________ pineapples.",
      "correctAnswer": "seventeen"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u7-h7",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "There are ___________ strawberries.",
      "correctAnswer": "sixteen"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u7-h8",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "There are ___________ blueberries.",
      "correctAnswer": "twenty"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u7-h9",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "There are ___________ bananas.",
      "correctAnswer": "twelve"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u7-h10",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "There are ___________ pears.",
      "correctAnswer": "fourteen"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c1",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "general",
      "correctAnswer": "general"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c2",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "maths",
      "correctAnswer": "maths"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c3",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "english",
      "correctAnswer": "english"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c4",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "physical",
      "correctAnswer": "physical"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c5",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "science",
      "correctAnswer": "science"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c6",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "history",
      "correctAnswer": "history"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c7",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "arts",
      "correctAnswer": "arts"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c8",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "geography",
      "correctAnswer": "geography"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c9",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "computer",
      "correctAnswer": "computer"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c10",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "music",
      "correctAnswer": "music"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c11",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "religious",
      "correctAnswer": "religious"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c12",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "project",
      "correctAnswer": "project"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c13",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "dictate",
      "correctAnswer": "dictate"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c14",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "visual",
      "correctAnswer": "visual"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c15",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "internet",
      "correctAnswer": "internet"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c16",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "outing",
      "correctAnswer": "outing"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c17",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "attention",
      "correctAnswer": "attention"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c18",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "listen",
      "correctAnswer": "listen"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c19",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "learn",
      "correctAnswer": "learn"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3u2-c20",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "improve",
      "correctAnswer": "improve"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c1",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "examine"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c2",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "escape"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c3",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "prison"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c4",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "gun"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c5",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "pickpocketing"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c6",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "fingerprint"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c7",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "ambulance"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c8",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "look for"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c9",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "shoplifting"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c10",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "evidence"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c11",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "burglary"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c12",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "arrest"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c13",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "witness"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c14",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "chase"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c15",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "victim"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c16",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "robbery"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c17",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "handcuff"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c18",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "fire engine"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c19",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "theft"
    },
    {
      "qid": "p5u12-c20",
      "questionType": "picture",
      "question": "",
      "correctAnswer": "thief"
    }
  ]

}